Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 7 Month(s)

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Electrical and Electronics

Notice Period: 3 Months

Engineering]

Navya Katta () Featured

Having 3.7 years of experience in Software Development/Knowledge of Agile Scrum methodology & Jira/

Capable of working on SQL, Postgresql,

Root Cause Analysis, ETL, Informatica, RDBMS, Requirement Analysis,

Data Warehousing, Data Modeling, PLSQL, SPs, Autosys



Current Designation: Technology Analyst

Current Company: Infosys

Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad

Pref. Location: Chennai, Bengaluru / Bangalore, Hyderabad Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: system admin,data analysis,agile methodology,data cleansing,data loader,root cause analysis,defect

management,requirement analysis,data warehousing,data

modeling,sql,informatica,netezza,unix,postgresql,RDBMS,AutoSys,PLSQL,technology analyst

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

A focused professional Software Developer offering 3.5 years of experience in IT Project Management, Data Analysis, Agile Methodology, Informatica Power Center, PLSQL, Stored Procedure, Autosys, Data Cleansing, Data Loader, Root Cause Analysis, Defect Management, Requirement Analysis, Requirement Analysis,

Data Warehousing, Data Modeling, Data Mapping, RDBMS, PostgresSQL, Unix, Python, OBIEE, Looker, DevOps

Work Experience

Infosys as Technology Analyst Oct 2020 to Till Date

Active involvement in meetings and Coordinating with onshore/business team for clarification on requirements.

Infosys Limited as Senior System Engineer Jun 2017 to Nov 2020

July-2019 to Present Infosys Limited Senior System Engineer Nov-2017 to June-2019 Infosys Limited System Engineer Jun-2017 to Oct-2017 Infosys Limited System Engineer Trainee ROLES & RESPONSIBILITIES:

- * Developing Quality, Reusable and error free code as per requirements.
- Writing Unit test cases for implemented functionalities.
- * Coordinating with testing team as and when code is deployed.
- * Active involvement in meetings and Coordinating with onshore/business team for clarification on requirements.
- Performing complex business level troubleshooting, root-cause analysis and solution development.
- * Good Experience in working under tight deadlines and with zero defects delivery and providing round the clock support.

PROJECTS:

Credit Bureau Reporting (CBR): On Going (July 2019 to Present)

Client(Confidential) is currently reporting Consumer's credit information using the data available in HOST (a Mainframe system) which doesn't have all the information required for Credit reporting that Causes in-accurate reporting. Also CDRT (Credit Dispute Research Team) user experience was not optimal as multiple systems have to be referred to locate information pertaining to M2 report related data for an account and Current M2 report was not compliant to CRRG (Credit Reporting Resource Guide) guidelines and included wrong values and incorrect scenarios because of which a big chunk of portfolio was not getting reported / incorrectly getting reported.

Since there is no History or not maintaining the updates/audit trial properly in Source Data Systems, CDRT users experienced more difficulty in identifying the root cause of an issue. In order to rectify these compliance issues and facilitate users to navigate through the credit data easily and review it to track the root cause of issues in order to correct the data prior to sending the information to CRAs(Credit Rating Agencies like Innovis, Equifax, Experian and Transunion) which can be called as Quality Control validation, Infosys has suggested to re-build the Metro2 report, compliance to CRRG using the data in BI system that benefitted client in several ways like Metro2 Reporting would be sticking to the CRRG guidelines, will be having Lesser credit disputes, Better experience for CDRT users as the entire information will be available in single System (BI) and Also they will be having better experience during the processes like account/consumer exclusion (automatic, manual), PHP updates (Automatic and Manual)due to maintenance of audit trials/proper history of updates, Business users will be having great experience in reviewing the Credit data through the Dashboards and Reports for various KPIs like Current balance, Amount Past Due, DOAI (Date of account information), PHP (Payment History profile) etc.. As they can easily walkthrough the data using the Dashboards and provided a facility to stop reporting any account/consumer prior to sending the credit information to CRAs if they find any issue with data corresponding to any account or consumer.

In this project, Data comes through various Sources like HOST (Mainframes), CEP (Salesforce), UCM (CRM-Siebel) and from Internal TFS Shared Drives and from Other third party vendors like LexisNexis, NBS, Br&Lee, DMS, VMS etc in the form of CSVs. All this data will be processed and loaded to BI Insight (Warehouse-HUB). Later this data will be processed per the Transformation rules and guide lines from CRRG and loaded to Various Dimensions, Fact and Summary tables in CBR Mart in order to generate the Metro2 file per CRRG guidelines to be shared with CRAs and to provide the data for analytics and Validations.

Responsibilities:

- * Creating mapping to achieve business requirement.
- * Migrate the code to higher environment and decide on the job scheduling.
- Performing tuning of SP's and Workflows

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electrical and Electronics Engineering) from Anil Neerukonda Institute of Technology & Sciences, Visakhapatnam in 2017

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience	
SQL, PL/SQL			2 Year(s) 6 Month(s)	
Informatica Power Center		0	3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
NETEZZA		0	2 Year(s) 6 Month(s)	
PostgreSQL		0	0 Year(s) 6 Month(s)	
AUTOSYS		0	2 Year(s) 6 Month(s)	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			
Telugu	Proficient			

Projects

Project Title: Toyota Financial Services

Client: Toyota

Nature of Employment: Full Time

Duration: Jan 2018 - Till Date
Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Project Details: Toyota Financial Services

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time